- Hello?
- Hey.
(Howard:)- How'd it go last night with my mom?
- Okay, I guess.
(Howard:)What time did you leave?
(Raj:)Actually, I'm still here.
- What? You spent the night?
- Yeah.
(Raj:)After dinner,
we watched a rerun of Rockford Files...
(Raj:)...and then she opened
a bottle of cream sherry...
(Raj:)...and the next thing I know
she was tucking me into your bed.
You wore my pajamas?
(Raj:)Mm-hm.
(Raj:)How do you sleep in these things?
Silk pajamas on satin sheets?
(Raj:)I slid out of the bed like three times.
Rajesh? You up?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)You ready for breakfast?
(Raj:)Oh, boy, breakfast.
(Howard:)Okay, Raj, listen.
You need to get out of there.
(Raj:)But I have a cream sherry hangover
and I smell blintzes.
(Howard:)If you don't leave now, she'll use food and
guilt to keep you there the rest of your life.